(this["webpackJsonphero-trivia"]=this["webpackJsonphero-trivia"]||[]).push([[0],{15:function(e,r,s){},16:function(e,r,s){},17:function(e,r,s){},19:function(e,r,s){},21:function(e,r,s){"use strict";s.r(r);var t=s(1),i=s.n(t),n=s(7),a=s.n(n),o=(s(15),s(16),[{Answer:"CGC",Question:"The leading 3rd-party grading service for comic books","Answer Letters":"3","Question Letters":"53",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Guaranty",Question:"CGC stands for Certified ________ Company","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"41",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Slab",Question:"Hard plastic shell for a graded comic book","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"42",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Golden",Question:"Comic book era from 1938-1956 is the ____ Age","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"45",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Silver",Question:"Comic book era from 1956-1970 is the ____ Age","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"45",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Bronze",Question:"Comic book era from 1970-1985 is the ____ Age","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"45",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Modern",Question:"Comic book era from 1985-Present is the ____ Age","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"48",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Platinum",Question:"The first age of comics, 1897-1938","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"34",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Gem",Question:"A comic with a grade of 10","Answer Letters":"3","Question Letters":"26",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Mint",Question:"A comic with a grade of 9.9","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"27",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Near Mint",Question:"A comic with a grade of 9.4, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"35",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Very Fine",Question:"A comic with a grade of 8.0, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"35",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Fine",Question:"A comic with a grade of 6.0","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"27",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Very Good",Question:"A comic with a grade of 4.0, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"35",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Good",Question:"A comic with a grade of 2.0 to 2.5","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"34",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Fair",Question:"A comic with a grade of 1.0","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"27",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Poor",Question:"A comic with a grade of 0.5","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"27",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Heritage",Question:"The largest comic book auction house","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"36",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Spider-Man",Question:"The most highly collected comic book series, the Amazing ________","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"65",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"writer",Question:"This person has control over the story","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"38",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"artist",Question:"This person draws the comic in pencil in black and white","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"56",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"penciler",Question:"The artist who does the original line drawings of the comic book","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"64",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"colorist",Question:"This person add color to the artist's B&W drawings","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"50",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"inker",Question:"The artist that uses  inks to draw over the penciler's artwork","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"62",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"letterer",Question:"This person adds the dialogue and sound effects","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"47",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"editor",Question:"This person makes sure everything is perfect before going to press","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"66",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"variant",Question:"A _______ cover is an alternative cover","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"39",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"annual",Question:"An ______, is an over-sized comic released once a year","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"54",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"one-shot",Question:"A _______ is complete story told in a single issue","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"35",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Mint",Question:"The comic is perfect in every way and has no damage or blemishes","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"64",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Key Issue",Question:"Issue that features the first appearance or deaths of a hero or villian, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"79",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"panel",Question:"One of the boxes on the page of a comic book","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"44",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"splash",Question:"A ______ panel consists of the entire page","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"42",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"manga",Question:"Japanese comics read right to left, not left to right","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"53",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Manhwa",Question:"Comics that originate from Korea","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"32",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Indie",Question:"An ____ comic refers to an independent publisher, not Marvel or DC","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"63",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Crossover",Question:"When story elements of two or more comic books come together","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"60",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Onomatopoeia",Question:"The sounds effects that you see in comics (eg. BOOM, POW, BANG etc)","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"67",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Diamond",Question:"Major distributor of comic books and graphic novels","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"51",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Ashcan",Question:"A prepublication draft of a comic book shown to potential advertisers","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"69",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Atom Age",Question:"Another name for the Golden Age of comics, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"49",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Cameo",Question:"When a character makes a brief appearance in a comic or movie","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"62",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Census",Question:"A _____ report shows collectors the scarcity of a comic book by grade","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"58",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Centerfold",Question:"The stapled, four-page middle sheet of a comic","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"46",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"CGC",Question:"Certified Guaranty Company","Answer Letters":"3","Question Letters":"26",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Authority",Question:"CCA stands for Comic Code _______","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"33",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Crossover",Question:"When one or more characters are in another character's title or story","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"69",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Foxing",Question:"Tiny brown spots on the cover / interior pages of a comic caused by mold","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"72",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Gatefold",Question:"A cover that folds into itself","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"30",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Genre",Question:"A grouping of comic books based on subject matter or style","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"58",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Giveaway",Question:"A comic book that at one time was given away as a promotional premium","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"69",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Origin",Question:"The story of a character's creation","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"35",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"CCA",Question:"Stands for the Comics Code Authority","Answer Letters":"3","Question Letters":"36",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"restoring",Question:"Treating a comic book to try to bring it back to its original condition","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"71",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"spine",Question:"The fold and stapled or glued edge of a comic book","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"52",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Silver",Question:"Comic books from the _____ era are highly collectible","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"53",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Amazing Spider-Man",Question:"The most actively collected comic book series, 3 wrds","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"52",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Stress",Question:"Lines from bends on or along the spine of a comic book","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"54",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"title",Question:"Page of a comic book that shows the name of the story ","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"54",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Amazing Fantasy",Question:"Spider-man appeared in this comic book first, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"15","Question Letters":"52",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Astonish",Question:"Hank Pym, Ant Man first appeared in Tales to ______","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"51",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Fantastic",Question:"Doctor Doom first appears in _______ Four","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"41",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Amazing",Question:"Peter Parker's Aunt May first appears in _______ Fantasy","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"56",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Mystery",Question:"Thor first appeared in Journey into ________","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"44",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Suspense",Question:"Iron-Man made his first appearance in Tales of ______","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"53",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Fantastic",Question:"The Watcher made his first appearance in _______ Four #4","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"56",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Kirby",Question:"Jack _____, one of creators of the Fantastic Four and X-Men","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"59",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Three  Million",Question:"Action Comics #1 (first appearance of Superman) recently sold for over _____ dollars, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"14","Question Letters":"92",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Action Comics",Question:"What comic book sold for over $3 million at aution, _______#1, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"69",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Spider-Man",Question:"Who is the most popular superhero","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"33",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Spider-Man",Question:"Who is the top grossing superhero of all time","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"45",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"NA",Series:"NA",Universe:"NA",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"McFarlane",Question:"Started at Marvel, then established his own indie comic book & collectibles company","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"83",Category:"Creators",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"NA",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Romita",Question:"John _______, a legendary artist of Marvel Silver Age of comics","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"63",Category:"Creators",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"NA",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Kirby",Question:'Jack _____, called the "King of Comics" was an artist, writer and editor at Marvel for over 40 years',"Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"101",Category:"Creators",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"NA",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Stan Lee",Question:"He was the editor in chief and creator of many of Marvel's most famous characters","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"81",Category:"Creators",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"NA",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Marvel",Question:"DC sued Marvel because they alleged Captain _______ was too similar to Superman","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"79",Category:"Fun Facts",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain Marvel",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Jason Momoa",Question:"Who played Aquaman in the 2018 movie of the same name","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"53",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Aquaman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Adam West\xa0",Question:"Who played Bruce Wayne/Batman in the 1966 firm Batman: The Movie, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"72",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Batman The Movie",Question:"Which movie featured Batman, Robin, Catwoman, Joker, Penguin & Riddler, 3 wrds","Answer Letters":"16","Question Letters":"78",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Ben Affleck\xa0",Question:"Who played Bruce Wayne / Batman in Batman v Superman: Dawn of Justice, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"77",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Meredith ",Question:"Burgess _______ played The Penquin in the 1966 firm Batman: The Movie","Answer Letters":"17","Question Letters":"69",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Burt Ward",Question:"Who played Dick Grayson/Robin in the 1966 firm Batman: The Movie, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"72",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Cathy Yan",Question:"Who directed the 2020 movie Birds of Prey, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"49",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Birds of Prey",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Cesar Romero\xa0",Question:"Who played The Joker in the 1966 firm Batman: The Movie, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"63",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Chris O'Donnell",Question:"Who played Dick Grayson/Robin in the 1997 movie, Batman & Robin, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"15","Question Letters":"71",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Christian Bale",Question:"Who played Bruce Wayne/Batman in the movie Batman Begins, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"14","Question Letters":"64",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Christian Bale\xa0",Question:"Who played Bruce Wayne/Batman in the 2008 film, The Dark Knight, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"15","Question Letters":"71",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Christian Bale\xa0",Question:"Who played Bruce Wayne/Batman in the 2012 film, The Dark Knight Rises, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"15","Question Letters":"77",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Christopher Reeve",Question:"Who played Clark Kent/Superman in the 1978 movie, Superman, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"17","Question Letters":"66",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Cillian Murphy",Question:"Who played Dr. Jonathan Crane / Scarecrow in Batman Begins, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"14","Question Letters":"66",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Danny DeVito\xa0",Question:"Who played the Penguin in Batman Returns, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"48",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Gene Hackman\xa0",Question:"Who played Lex Luther in the 1978 movie, Superman, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"57",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"George Clooney\xa0",Question:"Who played Batman in the 1997 movie Batman & Robin, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"15","Question Letters":"58",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Gorshin\xa0",Question:"Frank _______ played The Riddler in the 1966 firm Batman: The Movie","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"67",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Heath Ledger\xa0",Question:"Who played the Joker in the 2008 film, The Dark Knight, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"62",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Henry Cavill",Question:"Who played Clark Kent/Superman in Batman v Superman: Dawn of Justice, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"76",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Superman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Jack Nicholson\xa0",Question:"Who played the Joker in the 1989 Batman movie, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"15","Question Letters":"53",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Jim Carrey\xa0",Question:"Who played the Riddler in Batman Forever, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"48",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Lee Meriwether\xa0",Question:"Lee _______ played The Catwoman in the 1966 firm Batman: The Movie","Answer Letters":"15","Question Letters":"66",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Margot Robbie\xa0",Question:"Who played Dr. Harleen Quinzel/Harley Quinn in the 2020 movie Birds of Prey, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"14","Question Letters":"83",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Birds of Prey",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Michael Keaton\xa0",Question:"Who played the lead role in the 1989 Batman movie, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"15","Question Letters":"57",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Michael Keaton\xa0",Question:"Who played Bruce Wayne/Batman in Batman Returns, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"15","Question Letters":"55",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Michelle Pfeiffer",Question:"Who played Catwoman in Batman Returns, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"17","Question Letters":"45",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Schwarzenegger",Question:"Arnold ________ played Mr. Freeze in the 1997 movie Batman & Robin, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"14","Question Letters":"74",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Tim Burton\xa0",Question:"Who directed the 1989 Batman movie, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"42",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Tom Hardy",Question:"Who played Bane in the 2012 film, The Dark Knight Rises, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"63",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Tommy Lee Jones",Question:"Who played Two-Face in Batman Forever, 3 wrds","Answer Letters":"15","Question Letters":"45",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Charlize Theron",Question:"Who played the lead role in Atomic Blonde, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"15","Question Letters":"41",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Oni Press",Series:"Atomic Blonde",Universe:"Indie",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Coldest City",Question:'The movie Atomic Blonde was based on this graphic novel, "The ______", 2 wrds',"Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"77",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Oni Press",Series:"Atomic Blonde",Universe:"Indie",Difficulty:"Hard"},{Answer:"Evangeline Lilly",Question:"Who played the Wasp in the 2018 movie, Ant-Man and the Wasp","Answer Letters":"16","Question Letters":"59",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Ant-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Hard"},{Answer:"Andrew Garfield",Question:"Who played Peter Parker/Spider-man in the 2012 movie, The Amazing Spider-man, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"15","Question Letters":"84",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Black Panther",Question:"What superhero movie is the highest-grossing film directed by a Black filmmaker, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"87",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Black Panther",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Bradley Cooper",Question:"Who was the voice for Rocket in the 2014 film, Guardians of the Galaxy, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"14","Question Letters":"78",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Brie Larson",Question:"Who played Carol Danvers/Captain Marvel in the 2019 movie, Captain Marvel, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"81",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain Marvel",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Chadwick Boseman",Question:"Who played T'Challa / Black Panther in the 2018 movie Black Panther, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"16","Question Letters":"75",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Black Panther",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Chris Evans",Question:"Who played Captain American in the 2011 movie of the same name, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"70",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Chris Evans",Question:"Who played Captain American in the movie, Captain America Winter Soldier, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"72",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Chris Hemsworth\xa0",Question:"Who played Thor in the 2011 film, Thor, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"16","Question Letters":"46",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Thor",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Chris Pratt",Question:"Who played Peter Quill/Star-Lord in the 2014 film, Guardians of the Galaxy, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"82",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Cumberbatch",Question:"Benedict _______ played Doctor Strange in the 2016 movie of the same name","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"73",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Doctor Strange",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Dave Bautista",Question:"Who played Drax the Destroyer in the 2014 film, Guardians of the Galaxy, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"79",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Doug Jones\xa0",Question:"Who played the body for the Silver Surfer in Fantastic Four: Rise of the Silver Surfer, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"94",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Edward Norton",Question:"Who played the Hulk, in the 2008 film, The Incredible Hulk, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"66",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Hulk",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Hugh Jackman",Question:"Who played Logan in the 2013 film, The Wolverine, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"56",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Ioan Gruffudd",Question:"Who played Reed Richards in the 2005 movie, Fantastic Four, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"66",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Jamie Bell",Question:"Who played The Thing in the 2015 movie, Fantastic Four, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"62",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Jessica Alba\xa0",Question:"Who played Sue Storm in the 2005 movie, Fantastic Four, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"62",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Julian McMahon\xa0",Question:"Who played Victor Von Doom in the 2005 movie, Fantastic Four, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"15","Question Letters":"68",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Laurence Fishburne\xa0",Question:"Who played the voice of the Silver Surfer in Fantastic Four: Rise of the Silver Surfer, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"19","Question Letters":"94",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Michael B. Jordan",Question:"Who played Johnny Storm in the 2015 movie, Fantastic Four, 3 wrds","Answer Letters":"17","Question Letters":"65",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Michael B. Jordan\xa0",Question:"Who played Killmonger in the 2018 movie Black Panther, 3 wrds","Answer Letters":"18","Question Letters":"61",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Black Panther",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Miles Teller\xa0",Question:"Who played Reed Richards/Mr. Fantastic in the 2015 movie, Fantastic Four, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"80",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Nicolas Cage",Question:"Who starred as Ghost Rider in the 2007 movie, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"52",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Ghost Rider",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Patrick Stewart",Question:"Who played Xavier in the 2000 film, X-Men, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"15","Question Letters":"49",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Paul Rudd",Question:"Who helped write and also played Ant Man in the 2015 movie of the same name, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"75",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Ant-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Ryan Coogler",Question:"What African American director wrote and directed the 2018 movie, Black Panther, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"87",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Black Panther",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Ryan Reynolds\xa0",Question:"Who played Deadpool in the 2016 movie of the same name, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"14","Question Letters":"62",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Deadpool",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Scarlett Johansson",Question:"Who played Natasha Romanoff / Black Widow in the 2021 movie, Black Widow, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"18","Question Letters":"80",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Sebastian Stan",Question:"Who played Bucky Barnes in the movie, Captain America Winter Soldier, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"14","Question Letters":"76",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Tobey Maguire",Question:"Who played Peter Parker/Spider-man in the 2002 movie, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"60",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Tobey Maguire",Question:"Who played Peter Parker/Spider-man in the 2004 movie, Spider-man 2, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"74",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Tobey Maguire",Question:"Who played Peter Parker/Spider-man in the 2007 movie, Spider-man 3, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"74",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Toby Kebbell",Question:"Who played Victor Von Doom in the 2015 movie, Fantastic Four, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"68",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Tom Hiddleston\xa0",Question:"Who played Lokie in the 2011 film, Thor, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"15","Question Letters":"47",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Thor",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Tom Holland",Question:"Who played Peter Parker/Spider-man in the firm, Spider-Man: Far From Home, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"81",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Tom Holland",Question:"Who played Peter Parker/Spider-man in the firm, Spider-Man: Homecoming, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"78",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Tom Holland",Question:"Who played Peter Parker/Spider-man in the firm, Spider-Man: No Way Home, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"79",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Vin Diesel\xa0",Question:"Who was the voice for Groot in the 2014 film, Guardians of the Galaxy, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"77",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Zoe Saldana\xa0",Question:"Who played Gamora in the 2014 film, Guardians of the Galaxy, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"67",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Gal Gadot",Question:"Who played Wonder Woman in the 2017 film of the same name, 2 wrds ","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"66",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Wonder Woman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Jon Bernthal\xa0",Question:"Who played Frank Castle / Punisher in the 2017 Netflix series, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"69",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Punisher",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Keanu Reeves",Question:"Who played Constantine in the 2005 film of the same name, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"64",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Constantine",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Ron Perlman",Question:"Who played Hellboy in the 2004 film of the same name, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"60",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Dark Horse",Series:"Hellboy",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Ryan Reynolds",Question:"Who played the Green Lantern in the 2011 movie, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"54",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Green Lantern",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Val Kilmer",Question:"Who played Bruce Wayne/Batman in Batman Forever, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"55",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Warren Beatty",Question:"Who played Dick Tracy in the 1990 movie of the same name, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"64",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Tribune",Series:"Dick Tracy",Universe:"Indie",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Black",Question:"______ Cat, has sometimes been Spider-Man's enemy, ally, and love interest","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"12",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Amazing Spider-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Venom",Question:"A sentient alien\xa0symbiote\xa0with an amorphous form needs to bond with a host to survive ","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"86",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Amazing Spider-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Watson",Question:"Mary Jane _____, married Peter Parker/Spider-Man","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"48",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Amazing Spider-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Scott Lang",Question:"Ant-Man's secret identity, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"25",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Ant-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Wasp",Question:"Nadia Pym is ______","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"19",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Ant-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Ant Man",Question:"Scott Lang is also knowns as _______, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"10",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Ant-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Aquaman",Question:"Arthur Curry is also  _________","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"34",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Aquaman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Aquaman",Question:"The son of a lighthouse keeper and an Atlantean queen","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"53",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Aquaman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Aquaman",Question:"Monarch of an undersea realm","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"28",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Aquaman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Aquaman",Question:"Founding member of the Justice League","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"37",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Aquaman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Aquaman",Question:"Able to communicate with all sea life","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"37",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Aquaman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Scarlet",Question:"_____ Witch, twin sister of Quicksilver","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"39",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Hawkeye",Question:"A deaf super hero","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"17",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"SHIELD",Question:"A special\xa0law enforcement and\xa0counter-terrorism\xa0agency in the MCU","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"65",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Vision",Question:'An\xa0android\xa0built by Ultron to be the "perfect being" who helps defeat Ultron',"Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"76",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Mansion",Question:"Avenger's _____ is where these superheroes live","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"47",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Hawkeye",Question:"Clint Barton is _____","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"21",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Hogan",Question:"Happy _____ is Tony Starks driver, body guard, and assistant","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"60",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Hawkeye",Question:"Master archer, member of the Avengers","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"37",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Romanova",Question:"Natasha __________, also known as the Black Widow","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"49",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Black Widow",Question:"Natasha Romanoff is _____, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"25",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Fury",Question:"Nick _____, Director of SHIELD","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"30",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Coulson",Question:"Phil _____, SHIELD agent","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"24",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Ancient",Question:"The ______ One, is Soccer Supreme & Dr. Strange's mentor","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"56",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Avengers",Question:"The _______ is a team of Marvel superheroes","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"43",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Batgirl",Question:"Barbara Gordon was also known as","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"32",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batgirl",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Damian",Question:"Son of Bruce Wayne and Talia al Ghul","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"36",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Commissioner",Question:"James Gordon, Police ______ of Gotham City","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"42",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Gordon",Question:"James ______, Police Commission in Gotham City","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"46",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Batman",Question:"Also known as the Dark Knight","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"29",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Batman",Question:"Bruce Wayne is also known as","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"28",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Batman",Question:"Became a crime fighting superhero after witnessing his parents' murder","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"70",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Batman",Question:"A legendary superhero with no super powers","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"42",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Batman",Question:"Uses his skills and a high-tech arsenal to compensate for his lack of superpowers","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"81",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Batman",Question:"Superhero who made his debut appearance in Detective Comics #27 in 1939","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"71",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Batman",Question:"His side kicks include Robin and Alfred","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"39",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Batman",Question:"His adversaries include the Penguin and the Joker","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"49",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Fourteen",Question:"At what age did Bruce Wayne start training to become Batman?","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"60",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Gotham",Question:"What city does Batman protect and call home?","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"44",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Bruce Wayne",Question:"Batman's secret identity, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"24",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Pennyworth",Question:"What is Bruce Wayne's butler's last name?","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"41",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Alfred",Question:"Helps maintain Wayne Manor and the Bat Cave, first name","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"55",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Pennyworth",Question:"Former British army officer, field medic and Shakespearean actor who helps Batman","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"81",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Robin",Question:"Dick Grayson is also known as ","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"30",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Robin",Question:"Founding member of the Teen Titans and later became their leader","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"64",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Nightwing",Question:"When Robin grew up he became known as","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"37",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Batwoman",Question:"She quit the Army after being outed as a lesbian, this party-girl became a superhero after a chance encounter with Batman","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"121",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batwoman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Wakanda",Question:"Home of the Black Panther","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"25",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Black Panther",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Black Panther",Question:"T'Challa is ________, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"20",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Black Panther",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Klaue",Question:"Ulysses _____, in Black Panther","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"31",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Black Panther",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Winter",Question:"The Captain's buddy, the _______ Soldier","Answer Letters":"14","Question Letters":"15",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Winter Soldier",Question:"Bucky Barnes is the _______, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"14","Question Letters":"23",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"America",Question:"Captain ______, founding member of the Avengers","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"47",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Britain",Question:"Captain ______, the English version of Captain America","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"16",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Steve Rogers",Question:"Captain America's secret identity, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"33",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Helicarrier",Question:"Flying aircraft carrier, S.H.I.E.L.D.mobile command center","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"58",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"War Machine",Question:"James Rhodes is ________, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"24",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Captain America",Question:"Dresses in red, white & blue and known for his shield, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"15","Question Letters":"20",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Carter",Question:"Peggy _____, love interest of Captain America","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"45",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Falcon",Question:"Sam Wilson is the ________","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"26",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Captain America",Question:"Steve Rogers is ______, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"15","Question Letters":"22",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Sam Wilson",Question:"The secret identity of the 2nd Captain America, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"46",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Talos",Question:"A cunning spy of the Skrull Empire, a master shapeshifter","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"57",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain Marvel",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Marvel",Question:"Captain ______, the most powerful female super hero","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"51",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain Marvel",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Danvers",Question:"Carol ______, Captain Marvel's secret identity","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"46",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain Marvel",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Marvel",Question:"Carol Danvers is also known as Captain ________","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"47",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain Marvel",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Foggy",Question:"_____ Nelson, the Daredevil's law partner","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"41",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Daredevil",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Daredevil",Question:"A blind superhero who is a lawyer by day","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"40",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Daredevil",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Strange",Question:"Doctor _____","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"12",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Dr. Strange",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Strange",Question:"Doctor Strange first appeared in ______ Tales","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"45",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Dr. Strange",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Sanctorum",Question:"Doctor Strange's home is called Sanctum _______","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"47",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Dr. Strange",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Strange",Question:"Dr. Stephen _______","Answer Letters":"14","Question Letters":"19",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Dr. Strange",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Agamotto",Question:"Dr. Strange wears the Eye of _____ around his neck","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"50",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Dr. Strange",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Dormannu",Question:"Nemesis of Dr. Strange from the Dark Dimension","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"46",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Dr. Strange",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Hard"},{Answer:"New York",Question:"Spider-man protects this city, 2 words","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"38",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Wong",Question:"Protects the New York Sanctum with Doctor Strange","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"49",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Dr. Strange",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Levitation",Question:"The Cloak of ______ is worn by Dr. Strange","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"42",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Dr. Strange",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Invisible",Question:"_______ Woman, one of the Fantastic Four","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"40",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Fantastic",Question:"Mr. _______, can stretch his body like rubber","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"45",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Richards",Question:"Reed ________, leader of the Fantastic Four","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"43",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Thing",Question:"Stony giant who is one of the Fantastic Four","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"44",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Ghost",Question:"____ Rider, Marvel's motorcycle-riding superhero","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"47",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Ghost Rider",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Ghost Rider",Question:"Johnny Blaze is _______, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"23",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Ghost Rider",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Green Arrow",Question:"Oliver Queen is also the _______, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"24",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Green Arrow",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Green Arrow",Question:"He was stranded on a deserted island and learned to become a master archer to survive, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"78",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Green Arrow",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Green Arrow",Question:"Spoiled, thrill-seeking playboy who becomes a master archer, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"54",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Green Arrow",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Green Arrow",Question:"Arrow shooting member of the Justice League, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"43",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Green Arrow",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Green Lantern",Question:"Hal Jordan is also known as the, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"31",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Green Lantern",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Green Lantern",Question:"Is in charge of Sector 2814 after inheriting a ring, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"51",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Green Lantern",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Green Lantern",Question:"Alan Scott is known as the ________, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"26",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Green Lantern",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Green Lantern",Question:"Gets his super powers from a ring, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"33",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Green Lantern",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Green Lantern",Question:"Founding member of the Justice League, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"37",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Green Lantern",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Green Lantern",Question:"Recharges his powers through a magic lantern, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"44",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Green Lantern",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Infinity",Question:"_____ Stones allow whoever wields them to have god-like powers","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"62",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Drax",Question:"_____, the Destroyer","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"20",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Warlock",Question:'Adam ________,  a synthetic being created by human scientists named "The Enclave"',"Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"81",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Drax",Question:"Is motivated solely to destroy Thanos in revenge for the death of his family","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"76",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Rocket",Question:"Bio-engineered animal who is part of the Guardians of the Galaxy","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"64",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Drax",Question:"Created by Mentor & Kronos to destroy Thanos","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"44",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Punisher",Question:"Frank Castle is the __________","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"30",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Drax",Question:"His family was killed by Thanos, he now lives to get revenge","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"60",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Groot",Question:'Only says "I am _____"',"Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"22",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Star-Lord",Question:"Peter Quill is _______","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"22",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Raccoon",Question:"Rocket is a bio-engineered ______","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"33",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Halfworld",Question:"Rocket Raccoon comes from Planet ______","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"39",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Groot",Question:"Sentient alien tree that keeps the universe safe","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"48",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Yondo",Question:'Star Lord\'s "adopted" father',"Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"28",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Ego",Question:"Star Lord's father","Answer Letters":"3","Question Letters":"18",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Thanos",Question:"Wiped out half the population of the universe","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"45",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Star-Lord",Question:'Yondo\'s "adopted" son',"Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"21",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Duckworld",Question:"Howard the Duck comes from the planet","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"37",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Howard the Duck",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Cigars",Question:"Howard the Duck smokes _______","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"30",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Howard the Duck",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Hulk",Question:"Bruce Banner is also the _____","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"21",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Hulk",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Jones",Question:"Rick _____, Hulk's closest confidant","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"36",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Hulk",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Lockjaw",Question:"A giant Inhuman bulldog whose super abilities include teleportation","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"67",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Inhumans",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Inhumans",Question:"A group of\xa0Marvel superheroes\xa0whose stories focus on the royal family","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"69",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Inhumans",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Bolt",Question:"Black _____, king of the Inhumans, who must remain silent","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"57",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Inhumans",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Pepper",Question:"_____ Potts is Tony Stark's romantic interest","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"45",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Iron-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Howard Stark",Question:"Founder of Stark Industries, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"27",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Iron-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Rocket",Question:"Groot's best friend","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"19",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Iron-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Tony Stark",Question:"Iron-Man's secret identity, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"26",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Iron-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Jarvis",Question:"The loyal butler to the Stark family","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"36",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Iron-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Iron Man",Question:"Tony Stark is ______, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"20",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Iron-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Jessica",Question:"______ Jones, a superhero turned private investigator","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"53",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Jessica Jones",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Luke Cage",Question:"Failed prison experiment gave him unbreakable skin & superhuman strength, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"72",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Luke Cage",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Cage",Question:"Luke ____, married Jessica Jones","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"32",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Luke Cage",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Shang-Chi",Question:"Master of the Ten Rings","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"23",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Shang-Chi",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Fifteen",Question:'As of 2022, how many times has Superman "died" in the DCU',"Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"57",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Superman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Fifteen",Question:'As of 2022, how many times has Batman "died" in the DCU',"Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"55",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Red Sun",Question:"Aside from Kryptonite, _____ radiation is Superman's great weakness, 2 wrd","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"74",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Superman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Man of Steel",Question:"Superman is also known as _______, 3 wrds","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"41",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Superman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Krypton",Question:"Superman is also referred to as the Last Son of ______","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"54",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Superman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Doomsday",Question:"This supervillain killed Superman in combat","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"43",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Superman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Kryptonite",Question:"Superman's main weakness is\xa0_____, radioactive shards of his former home planet","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"79",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Superman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Tomorrow",Question:"Superman is also known as the Man of _______","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"44",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Superman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Shang-Chi",Question:"The first Asian American superhero","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"30",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Shang-Chi",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Black Panther",Question:"The first black superhereo, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"34",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Black Panther",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Meteor Man\xa0",Question:"This 1993 movie  was the first movie to feature a black superhero, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"73",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Indie",Series:"Meteor Man",Universe:"Indie",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Ten Rings",Question:"Shang-Chi gets his powers from the ________, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"51",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Shang-Chi",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Silver Surfer",Question:"Saved his homeworld from Galactus, by agreeing to find other planets for him to devour, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"94",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Silver",Question:"_____ Surfer, servant of Galactus who bretrayed him to save Earth","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"65",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Silver Surfer",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Silver Surfer",Question:"An alien with metallic skin who travels through space riding a surfboard, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"72",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Silver Surfer",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Waller",Question:"Amanda ________ is in charge of the Suicide Squad","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"49",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Suicide Squad",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Suicide",Question:"Amanda Waller is in charge of the ________Squad","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"47",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Suicide Squad",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Suicide Squad",Question:"A rapid response team of criminals and\xa0supervillains controlled by bombs in their necks, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"87",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Suicide Squad",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Enchantress",Question:"This demonic witch battles the Suicide Squad","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"44",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Suicide Squad",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Superman",Question:"Rocketed to Earth as an infant from the doomed planet Krypton","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"61",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Superman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Superman",Question:"Adopted by the Kent family and raised in America's heartland","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"60",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Superman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Superman",Question:"Known as Kal-El at birth","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"24",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Superman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Superman",Question:"He is faster than a speeding bullet, more powerful than a locomotive, and able to leap tall buildings in a single bound","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"119",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Superman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Metropolis",Question:"The city where Superman & Clark Kent live","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"41",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Superman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Clark Kent",Question:"He is a field reporter for the Daily Planet, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"43",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Superman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Supergirl",Question:"Superman's cousin and last survivor of Krypton's Argo City","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"58",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Superman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Lois Lane",Question:"She was the first reporter to interview Superman after he appeared in Metropolis, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"80",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Superman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Lois Lane",Question:"Married to Clark Kent and has a son named Jon, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"45",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Superman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Krypto",Question:"Superman's loyal canine companion and sidekick","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"46",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Superman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Krypto",Question:"Dog that escaped Krypton's destruction and came to Earth","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"56",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Superman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Krypto",Question:"Dog that can fly, has super-strength, super-speed and super-breath","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"66",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Superman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Krypto",Question:"Family pooch who loves to play with Lois and Clark's son","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"56",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Superman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"TMNT",Question:"Short for Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"38",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Mirage Studios",Series:"Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Spiderman",Question:"Your friendly neighborhood _______","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"34",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"The Amazing Spider-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"The Flash",Question:"Barry Allen is also knowns as ________, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"20",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"The Flash",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"The Flash",Question:"Wally West adopted this superhero name to honor his uncle who died saving the Universe, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"86",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"The Flash",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"The Flash",Question:"A forensic scientist with super-speed, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"37",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"The Flash",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Central City",Question:"The city that the Flash/Barry Allen protect and call home, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"57",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"The Flash",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"The Flash",Question:"The fastest man alive and founding member of the Justice League","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"63",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"The Flash",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Punisher",Question:"A vigilante who wears a skull like logo on his body armor","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"57",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"The Punisher",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Castle",Question:"Frank _______, the Punisher","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"27",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"The Punisher",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Suspense",Question:"Hawkeye made his first appearance in Tales of ______","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"52",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Thor",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Heimdall",Question:"he guards the Bifrost Bridge","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"28",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Thor",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Valkyrie",Question:"The goddess Brunnhilde, one of Asgard's mightiest warriors","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"58",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Thor",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Asgard",Question:"The home of Thor, Odin and the Valkyrie","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"39",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Thor",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Loki",Question:"Thor's adopted brother","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"22",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Thor",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Wonder Woman",Question:"An Amazon princess, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"18",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Wonder Woman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Wonder Woman",Question:"Superhero who believes in diplomacy, peace, and love, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"52",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Wonder Woman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Wonder Woman",Question:"The first prominent female superhero, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"36",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Wonder Woman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Wonder Woman",Question:"Also known as Princess of the Amazons, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"37",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Wonder Woman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"All-Star",Question:"Wonder Woman made her first appearance in which comic book series in 1948","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"73",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Wonder Woman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Diana",Question:"Wonder Woman's first name","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"25",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Wonder Woman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Wonder Woman",Question:"This superhero wears bracelets and uses a lasso of truth, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"56",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Wonder Woman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Paradise Island",Question:"Place where Wonder Woman grew up, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"15","Question Letters":"32",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Wonder Woman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Xavier",Question:" _____ Institute is the home of the X-Men","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"41",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Professor",Question:"_______ X is the leader of the X-Men","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"36",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Hercules",Question:"A character based on Greek mythology and a member of the Avengers","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"65",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Nightcrawler",Question:"A devout Catholic with a demonic appearance","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"43",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Beast",Question:"A X-Men mutant possessing animal-like strength and agility","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"58",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Beast",Question:"Dr. Hank McCoy is also the ________","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"35",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Frost",Question:"Emma _____, once a villain, later joins the X-Men","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"49",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Grey",Question:"Jean ____, member of the X-Men","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"30",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Shawowcat",Question:"Kitty Pryde is also _________, and a member of the X-Men","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"56",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Vibranium",Question:"metal prized for its virtually indestructable nature, only found in\xa0Wakanda","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"75",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"X-Men",Question:"The Beast first appeared in ","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"28",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Danger",Question:"The X-Men train in the specially built_______ Room","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"50",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Angel",Question:"Warren Kenneth Worthington III is an X-man, also known as","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"57",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Cannonball",Question:"A\xa0mutant\xa0who can fly at\xa0jet\xa0speeds encased in an impenetrable\xa0force field, he was a founding member of the New Mutants","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"118",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"John Dusk",Question:"A superhero/cop turned vigilante from Avatar Press","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"50",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Avatar Press",Series:"Absolution",Universe:"None",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Invincible",Question:"A teenage Viltrumite/Human hybrid","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"33",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Skybound",Series:"Invincible",Universe:"None",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Invincible",Question:"Superhero, son of Omni-Man","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"26",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Skybound",Series:"Invincible",Universe:"None",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Grayson",Question:"Mark _____ is also known as Invisible","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"37",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Skybound",Series:"Invincible",Universe:"None",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Spawn",Question:"This superhero is a highly trained assassin, murdered by his employer/former friend who made a deal with the devil to see his wife again","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"136",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Image",Series:"Spawn",Universe:"ICU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Simmons",Question:"Francis ______, sold his sold to a demon of hell in order to see his wife again","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"79",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Image",Series:"Spawn",Universe:"ICU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"McFarlane",Question:"Todd _______, creator of Spawn and founder of Image Comics","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"58",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Image",Series:"Spawn",Universe:"ICU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Spawn",Question:"A Hellspawn vigilante superhero","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"31",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Image",Series:"Spawn",Universe:"ICU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Estacado",Question:"Jackie _______ is an ex-Mafia hitman, ex-Don of a crime family and ex-Dictator of a country","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"91",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Top Cow",Series:"The Darkness",Universe:"None",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Pezzini",Question:"Detective Sara ________ was forever changed the day she came into contact with the Witchblade, an ancient mystical artifact.","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"124",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Top Cow",Series:"Witchblade",Universe:"None",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Nottingham",Question:"Trained since birth to kill, Ex-SAS and MI5: Ian ______is one of the most dangerous assassins","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"93",Category:"Super Heros",Publisher:"Top Cow",Series:"Witchblade",Universe:"None",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Osborn",Question:"Harry ______, Peter Parker's best friend for a while","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"52",Category:"Supporting Roles",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Norman",Question:"____ Osborn, global industrialist and the Green Goblin","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"54",Category:"Supporting Roles",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Aunt May",Question:"Peter Parker's aunt-by-marriage and one of the most important people in his life, wrds","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"86",Category:"Supporting Roles",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Uncle Ben",Question:"Peter Parker's relative who died and inspired him to use his powers for good, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"84",Category:"Supporting Roles",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"The Avengers",Question:"A group of Marvel superheroes whose membership is constantly changing, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"69",Category:"Teams",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"The Avengers",Question:"Famous group of superheroes created by Stan Lee and Jack Kirby, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"62",Category:"Teams",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"The Avengers",Question:"originally consisted of\xa0Iron Man,\xa0Ant-Man,\xa0Hulk,\xa0Thor\xa0and the\xa0Wasp","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"66",Category:"Teams",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"The Avengers",Question:"This team's most recent members include Iron Man, Hulk, Hawkeye, Captain America, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"89",Category:"Teams",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Extraordinary",Question:"League of _________  Gentlemen","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"30",Category:"Teams",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Extraordinary",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Fantastic Four",Question:"Gained\xa0superpowers\xa0after exposure to\xa0cosmic rays\xa0during a scientific mission to outer space, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"14","Question Letters":"91",Category:"Teams",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Fantastic Four",Question:"Group who regularly battled with Dr. Doom and Galactus, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"14","Question Letters":"54",Category:"Teams",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Fantastic Four",Question:"Mr. Fantastic, Invisible Woman, Human Torch & Thing, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"14","Question Letters":"51",Category:"Teams",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Authority",Question:"The _______, a Wildstorm universe super team primarily comprised of former Stormwatch members","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"93",Category:"Teams",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Stormwatch",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Suicide Squad",Question:"A fictional\xa0antihero\xa0team published by\xa0DC Comics, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"48",Category:"Teams",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Suicide Squad",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Suicide Squad",Question:"A team of incarcerated\xa0supervillains\xa0who do high-risk\xa0missions in exchange for pardons or early parole, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"102",Category:"Teams",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Suicide Squad",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Suicide Squad",Question:"Harley Quinn is the unofficial leader of this team, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"50",Category:"Teams",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Suicide Squad",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Task Force X",Question:"Suicide Squad is also known as ________ 3 wrds","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"39",Category:"Teams",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Suicide Squad",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Suicide Squad",Question:"This team originally appeared in six issues of\xa0The Brave and the Bold 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"69",Category:"Teams",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Suicide Squad",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Super Friends",Question:"An American\xa0animated TV series\xa0that ran from 1973 to 1985\xa0on\xa0ABC\xa0on Saturday mornings, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"85",Category:"Teams",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Super Friends",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Teenage Mutant",Question:"_________ Ninja Turtles, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"14","Question Letters":"23",Category:"Teams",Publisher:"Mirage Studios",Series:"Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Ninja Turtles",Question:"Leonardo,\xa0Raphael,\xa0Donatello\xa0and\xa0Michelangelo; teenage mutant _________","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"71",Category:"Teams",Publisher:"Mirage Studios",Series:"Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"The Boys",Question:"A CIA\xa0squad, led by\xa0Billy Butcher\xa0and with help from Hughie Campbell, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"68",Category:"Teams",Publisher:"DC",Series:"The Boys",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"The Boys",Question:"Comic book series adapted by\xa0Amazon into a\xa0TV series\xa0that premiered in July 2019, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"80",Category:"Teams",Publisher:"DC",Series:"The Boys",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Umbrella Academy",Question:"Team made up of Spaceboy,\xa0Kraken,\xa0Rumor,\xa0S\xe9ance,\xa0Number Five,\xa0Horror, and\xa0White Violin, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"16","Question Letters":"94",Category:"Teams",Publisher:"Dark Horse",Series:"The Umbrella Academy",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Umbrella",Question:"________ Academy, a dysfunctional family of\xa0superheroes assembled by Sir Reginald Hargeeves","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"91",Category:"Teams",Publisher:"Dark Horse",Series:"The Umbrella Academy",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Ultron",Question:"A self-aware, highly intelligent robot who develops a\xa0god complex\xa0and A grudge against his creator\xa0Hank Pym","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"107",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Struker",Question:"Baron von _______ is an enemy of SHIELD and the Avengers","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"56",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Hydra",Question:"Baron von Strucker's terrorist organization prominent in the MCU","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"64",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Dormammu",Question:"One of Doctor Strange's fiercest adversaries","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"43",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Doctor Strange",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Dormammu",Question:"A primordial inter-dimensional entity who is the ruler of the\xa0Dark Dimension","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"76",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Doctor Strange",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Dark Dimension",Question:"Dormammu is ruler of the ________, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"14","Question Letters":"41",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Doctor Strange",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Agamotto",Question:"Doctor Strange used the Eye of _______ to trap Dormammu, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"45",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Doctor Strange",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Puppet",Question:"The ______ Master, first appeared in Fantastic Four #8","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"50",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Skrulls",Question:"A race of extraterrestrial shapeshifters who appear in many Marvel comic series","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"78",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Galactus",Question:"A\xa0cosmic entity\xa0that consumes planets to sustain its life force","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"63",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Galactus",Question:"An enormous space-travelling villian who feeds by draining living planets of their energy","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"63",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Ronan",Question:"______ the Accuser, is the Supreme Accuser of the\xa0Kree Empire and works with Thanos","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"83",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Thanos",Question:"A powerful villian in the\xa0MCU, he has A twisted moral compass and thinks his actions are justified","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"99",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Bane",Question:"What villian was sentence to life in prison for crimes committed by his father","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"78",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Magneto",Question:"This villain is able to was a Holocaust survivor is able to control magnetic fields","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"83",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Black Adam",Question:"5,000 years receiving the powers of Egyptian\xa0gods  ______ is freed from his tomb and unleashes his unique form of justice on the world","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"134",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Black Adam",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Dwayne Johnson\xa0",Question:"Who plays Black Adam in the 2022 film of the same name, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"15","Question Letters":"62",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Black Adam",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Doctor Octopus",Question:"Otto Octavius is also known as _____, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"14","Question Letters":"44",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Otto Octavius",Question:"Doctor Octopus was originally Dr. _____, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"47",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Canadian",Question:"What nationality is Woverine","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"28",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Black Widow",Question:"This superhero was an agent for the Russian government before joining the Avengers, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"90",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Jason Todd",Question:"This juvenile delinquent stole the wheels off the Batmobile, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"67",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Dead Pool",Question:"This anti-hero is known for his flippant attitude and sense of humor, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"76",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Deadpool",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Punisher",Question:"This anti-hero got his start fighting Spider-Man, but soon became a popular hero in his own right","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"97",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Punisher",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Deadpool",Question:"Which superhero knows he is a comic book character and is famous for breaking the fourth wall","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"93",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Deadpool",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"War Machine",Question:"Iron Man's side kick, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"28",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Iron-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Falcon",Question:"Sam Wilson, aka______ proved he's more than just Captain America's sidekick","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"75",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Flash Thompson",Question:"He relentlessly bullied Peter Parker for years, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"14","Question Letters":"54",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Canadian",Question:"What nationality is Deadpool","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"28",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Deadpool",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"British",Question:"What nationality is Blade","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"25",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Blade",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"British",Question:"What nationality is Spider-Woman","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"32",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Wong",Question:"Doctor Strange's side kick","Answer Letters":"4","Question Letters":"26",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Doctor Strange",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Thanos",Question:"A genocidal warlord from\xa0Titan, whose goals was to bring stability to the universe by wiping out half of all life at every level","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"128",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Thanos",Question:"father of Gamora\xa0and\xa0Nebula","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"27",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Thanos",Question:"With a single snap, _______ wiped out half of all life forms in the galaxy","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"74",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Collector",Question:"Created a massive museum of life forms and artifacts from across the MCU","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"72",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Collector",Question:"Taneleer Tivan is also known as the\xa0_________","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"45",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Maximus",Question:"Both a member of and antagonist to the\xa0Inhumans","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"47",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Inhumans",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Barracuda",Question:"A ruthless criminal and assissin who hunted the Punisher","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"56",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Punisher",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Kraven",Question:"_______, the Hunter, one of Spider-Man's advesaries","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"51",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Rhino",Question:"A green colored villian with a horn on his head, early Spider-Man advesary","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"74",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Sinister Six",Question:"A group originallly composed of Doc Oc, Vulture, Electro, Mysterio, Sandman & Kraven, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"92",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Morbius",Question:"A vampire inspired Spider-Man advesary, he became an antihero\xa0with his own series","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"81",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Kingpin",Question:"A\xa0crime overlord, advesary of Spider-Man,Daredevil,\xa0Hawkeye, andthe\xa0Punisher","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"76",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Green Goblin",Question:"A\xa0Halloween-themed supervillain that flies on A hoverboard, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"66",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Vulture",Question:"Adrian Toomes is the flying supervillian called the _______","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"59",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Octopus",Question:"Doctor _____, Spider-man's first villian, aka Doc Oc","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"52",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Green Goblin",Question:"Norman Osborn turns into the ________, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"45",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Molten Man",Question:"One of Spider-Man's early foes, his body can generate extreme heat and radiation, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"88",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Chameleon",Question:"Spider-man's first adversay in The Amazing Spider-Man #1","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"56",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Enforcers",Question:"Team of villians originally consisting of Montana, the\xa0Ox, and\xa0Fancy Dan","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"72",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Sinister",Question:"The _______ Six, a group of villians organized by Doctor Octopus","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"64",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Absorbing",Question:"______ Man, can take on the properties of any material he touches","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"65",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Thor",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Destroyer",Question:"An animated suit of Asguardian armor that plagues Thor","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"54",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Thor",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Omega",Question:"_______ Red, a Russian serial killer, the USSR's attempt to combat Captain America","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"82",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Hard"},{Answer:"Juggernaut",Question:"A villian whose head is like A battering ram","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"44",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Cerebro",Question:"Device created by Professor X to detect humans and mutants","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"58",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Deathstrike",Question:"Lady _______, a foe of the X-Men, especially Wolverine","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"54",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Hard"},{Answer:"Sinister",Question:"Mr. ______, dreamed of creating the ultimate mutant, rhymes with minister","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"73",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Hard"},{Answer:"Sentinels",Question:"Mutant-hunting\xa0robots, usually advesaries of the\xa0X-Men","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"55",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Mastermind",Question:"Jason Wyngrade, is also the supervillian _______","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"48",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"NA",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Collector",Question:"This brother is knowns as the Grandmaster","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"41",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Grandmaster",Question:"His brother is knowns as the Collector","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"38",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Guardians of the Galaxy",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Avengers Endgame",Question:"As of 2022, what is the highest grossing superhero movie with over $27 billion in ticket sales, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"16","Question Letters":"103",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Batgirl",Question:"A vigilante in\xa0Gotham City\xa0and the daughter of police commissioner James Gordon","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"79",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Batman",Question:"A wealthy socialite in Gotham City who moonlights as a crimefighting vigilante","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"78",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Barbara Gordon",Question:"Batgirl's secret identity, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"14","Question Letters":"33",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Shazam",Question:"What word does 14-year old Billy Batson shout out to become an adult superhero","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"78",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Shazam",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Adamantium",Question:"What fictional metal alloy is virtually indestructable and is bonded to Wolverine's skeleton","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"92",Category:"Fun Facts",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Adamantium",Question:"What fictional metal alloy is virtually indesctructable and is part of Ultron's outer shell","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"91",Category:"Fun Facts",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Deadpool",Question:"What blockbuster Marvel superhero started off as a parody of a DC villlian","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"74",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Deadpool",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Deadpool",Question:"What superhero is afraid of cows and clowns?","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"44",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Deadpool",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Deadpool",Question:'What superhero is also known as the "merc with a mouth"',"Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"55",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Deadpool",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Aquaman\xa0",Question:"What superhero was born with the Curse of Kordax","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"48",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Aquaman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Abomination",Question:"What super villain was created when Emil Blonsky accidentally exposed himself to a concentrated burst of gamma rays","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"115",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Hulk",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Starfire",Question:"What superhero grew up on the planet Tamaran","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"44",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Teen Titans",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Iron Man",Question:"Edwin Jarvis serves as butler to what superhero","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"47",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Iron-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Hawkgirl",Question:"Which golden age superheroine was inhabited by the soul of an ancient Egyptian princess","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"87",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Hawkman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Phantom\xa0",Question:"The _____ was the first costumed superhero and appeared in 1936","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"63",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Indie",Series:"The Phantom",Universe:"ICU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Iron Fist",Question:"Who is Luke Cage's best friend and longtime partner in crime-fighting","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"69",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Luke Cage",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Metamorpho",Question:"What superhero gained his powers after being exposed to the Orb of Ra","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"69",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Metamorpho",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Metamorpho",Question:"_______, the Element Man, can shapeshift and change himself into any\xa0element\xa0or combination of elements in the human body","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"",Category:"",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Metamorpho",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Black Panther",Question:"T'Challa, the king of Wakanda, is also known as what superhero","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"62",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Black Panther",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Baxter Building",Question:"What building served as the original headquarters for the Fantastic Four","Answer Letters":"15","Question Letters":"72",Category:"Fun Facts",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Quicksilver",Question:"Who is the Scarlet Witch's twin brother","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"39",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Crystal\xa0",Question:"What member of the Inhumans did Johnny Storm date","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"49",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"X-Men",Question:"______ #1 (Vol. 2) is the best-selling comic book of all time, with 8.1 million copies sold","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"91",Category:"Collecting",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Hard"},{Answer:"Fredric Wertham",Question:"What German-American psychiatrist warned in a 1954 that comic books caused  juvenile delinquency, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"15","Question Letters":"104",Category:"Fun Facts",Publisher:"",Series:"",Universe:"",Difficulty:"Hard"},{Answer:"Sanctum Sanctorum",Question:"What is the name of Doctor Strange's home in Greenwich Village","Answer Letters":"17","Question Letters":"62",Category:"Locations",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Doctor Strange",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Daily Bugle",Question:"What newspaper does Peter Parker work for, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"49",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Ben Grimm",Question:"Who was Reed Richards' roommate in college, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"50",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Ultron",Question:"This villain created the Vision to destroy the villian's creator","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"64",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Cesar Romero",Question:"Who played the Joker in the 1960s\xa0Batman\xa0television series","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"58",Category:"Movies",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Dave Sim",Question:"What writer/artist wrote and drew over 300 issues of a single comic book, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"80",Category:"Creators",Publisher:"Indie",Series:"Cerebus",Universe:"ICU",Difficulty:"Hard"},{Answer:"Cerebus",Question:"An anthropromorphic aardvark who was originally created to be a parody of Marvel's Conan the Barbarian","Answer Letters":"","Question Letters":"102",Category:"Creators",Publisher:"Indie",Series:"Cerebus",Universe:"ICU",Difficulty:"Hard"},{Answer:"Rick Jones",Question:"What teenager did Bruce Banner save from a gamma bomb","Answer Letters":"10","Question Letters":"53",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Hulk",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Barack Obama",Question:"What U. S. President appears in\xa0The Amazing Spider-Man #583, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"67",Category:"Fun Facts",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"yellow",Question:"What color is Robin's cape","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"26",Category:"Fun Facts",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Howard the Duck",Question:"What superhero has a girlfriend named Beverly Switzler, 3 wrds","Answer Letters":"15","Question Letters":"62",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Howard the Duck",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Starfox",Question:"What member of the Avengers is brother to the supervillain Thanos","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"65",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Avengers",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Jessica Jones",Question:"What character marries Luke Cage, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"13","Question Letters":"40",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Luke Cage",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Bullseye",Question:"Who killed Elektra","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"18",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Daredevil",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"batman",Question:"Who would you call if Mr. Freeze attacked","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"41",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"radioactive",Question:"Spider-man got his powers after being bitten by a _______ spider","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"64",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Uncle Ben",Question:'Who said, "With great power comes great responsibility," 2 wrds',"Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"63",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"responsibility",Question:"With great power comes great ________","Answer Letters":"14","Question Letters":"37",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Joe Chill",Question:"Who killed Thomas and Martha Wayne","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"34",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Malekith",Question:"Who is the villain of \u2018Thor: The Dark World?","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"44",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Thor",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Shadow",Question:"The ______said, \u201cWho knows what evil lurks in the hearts of men?","Answer Letters":"6","Question Letters":"64",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Indie",Series:"The Shadow",Universe:"ICU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Captain America",Question:"Who has an indestructible shield, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"15","Question Letters":"40",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Thing",Question:"The _____ is the superhero who can no longer transform back into human","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"70",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Storm",Question:"Who is the superhero who can manipulate and resist the weather","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"62",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"X-Men",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Riddler",Question:"In Batman Forever, which villain did\xa0Jim Carrey\xa0play","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"52",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Flash",Question:"The _____ also known as the Scarlet Speedster","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"45",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Flash",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Humanite",Question:"Ultra ______ is the first super villain in Superman","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"51",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Superman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Dick Grayson",Question:"What was the secret identity of the first Robin, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"55",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Batman",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Agamotto",Question:"The Eye of _______ contains the Time Stone","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"42",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Doctor Strange",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Frost Giant",Question:"What species is Loki, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"28",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Thor",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Wade Wilson",Question:"What Deadpool's real name, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"33",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Deadpool",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Neurosurgeon",Question:"What type of Doctor is Stephen Strange","Answer Letters":"12","Question Letters":"38",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Doctor Strange",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Thing",Question:"The _____ likes to say, \u201cIt\u2019s clobbering time!","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"46",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Fantastic Four",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Kingpin",Question:"Who is the Daredevil's arch nemesis","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"35",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Daredevil",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Vietnam",Question:"Where does Iron Man\u2019s origin story begin in the comic book series","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"65",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Iron-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Afghanistan",Question:"Where does Iron Man\u2019s origin story begin in the movies","Answer Letters":"11","Question Letters":"54",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Iron-Man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Phantom\xa0",Question:"The _______ was the first superhero ever","Answer Letters":"8","Question Letters":"40",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Indie",Series:"The Phantom",Universe:"ICU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"vibranium",Question:"What is Captain America\u2019s shield made of","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"40",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Captain America",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Mjolnir",Question:"What is the name of Thor\u2019s hammer","Answer Letters":"7","Question Letters":"33",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Thor",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Medium"},{Answer:"Chameleon",Question:"Who was the first super villain Spider-man battles in the comic book","Answer Letters":"9","Question Letters":"68",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Fantastic Four",Question:"What team of superheroes does Spider-Man battle in Issue #1, 2 wrds","Answer Letters":"14","Question Letters":"67",Category:"Super Heroes",Publisher:"Marvel",Series:"Spider-man",Universe:"MCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:"Joker",Question:"Who was the first villain Batman encountered in the comic book","Answer Letters":"5","Question Letters":"62",Category:"Villians",Publisher:"DC",Series:"Batman",Universe:"DCU",Difficulty:"Easy"},{Answer:""}]),u=s(2),l=(s(17),s(0));function h(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:"-",r=arguments.length>1&&void 0!==arguments[1]&&arguments[1],s=arguments.length>2&&void 0!==arguments[2]&&arguments[2],i=Object(t.useState)(r),n=Object(u.a)(i,2),a=n[0],o=n[1],l=Object(t.useState)(s),h=Object(u.a)(l,2),y=h[0],f=h[1],w=Object(t.useState)(""),A=Object(u.a)(w,2),c=A[0],d=A[1],C=Object(t.useState)(e),m=Object(u.a)(C,2),v=m[0],S=m[1],L=[],g={state:a,setState:o,special:y,setSpecial:f,letter:v,setLetter:S,position:L,attemptLetter:c,setAttempt:d};return g}function y(e){var r="",s="";return e.context.state?(r="Cell",r+=e.context.special?" Cell-Glow":" Cell-Input",s=e.context.special?e.context.letter:Object(l.jsx)("input",{type:"text",onFocus:function(){var r;r=e.context,(0,e.setRow)(r.position[0]),console.log("row",r.position[0])},onChange:function(r){!function(e,r){r.setSpecial(e.target.value.toLowerCase()==r.letter.toLowerCase())}(r,e.context,e.setRow)}})):r="Space",Object(l.jsx)("td",{className:r,children:Object(l.jsx)("p",{className:"CellContent",children:s})})}s(19);function f(e){return Object(l.jsx)(c,{dimensions:C(e),word:e.word,data:e.data})}var w=[];function A(e){w=[];for(var r=parseInt(e.dimensions.width/2),s=0;s<e.dimensions.height;s++){for(var t=[],i=e.data[s].Answer,n=i.indexOf(e.data[s].Letter),a=0,o=0;o<e.dimensions.width;o++){var u={},f=r-n;o>=f&&o<r+i.length-n?(u=h(i[a],!0,o-f==e.data[s].Index),a++):u=h(""),u.position=[s,o],t.push(u)}w.push(t)}var A=Object(l.jsx)("tbody",{children:w.map((function(r,s){return t=r,i=s,Object(l.jsx)("tr",{children:t.map((function(r,s){return Object(l.jsx)(y,{setRow:e.context.setRow,context:r},"".concat(i,",").concat(s))}))},i);var t,i}))});return A}function c(e){var r=Object(t.useState)(0),s=Object(u.a)(r,2),i={row:s[0],setRow:s[1]};return Object(l.jsxs)("div",{className:"App",children:[Object(l.jsx)("div",{className:"background-image"}),Object(l.jsxs)("div",{className:"Board-title",children:[Object(l.jsx)("div",{className:"neon-orange",children:"Hero"}),Object(l.jsx)("div",{className:"neon-blue",children:"Trivia"})]}),Object(l.jsxs)("div",{className:"caption",children:["Use",Object(l.jsx)("b",{children:"\xa0TAB\xa0"}),"to easily jump to the next letter!"]}),Object(l.jsx)("table",{className:"Board",children:Object(l.jsx)(A,{dimensions:e.dimensions,word:e.word,data:e.data,context:i})}),Object(l.jsx)(d,{data:e.data,context:i})]})}function d(e){var r=e.data[e.context.row].Question;return Object(l.jsx)("div",{className:"Question-container",children:Object(l.jsx)("div",{className:"Question-content",children:r})})}function C(e){var r,s=0;return r=e.word.length,e.data.forEach((function(e){s<e.Answer.length&&(s=e.Answer.length)})),{width:2*s,height:r}}var m=s(6),v=s.n(m),S=s(10),L=s(8),g=s(9),M=[];function Q(){document.getElementById("file-selector").addEventListener("change",(function(e){!function(e){_.apply(this,arguments)}(e.target.files[0])}))}function _(){return(_=Object(L.a)(v.a.mark((function e(r){var s;return v.a.wrap((function(e){for(;;)switch(e.prev=e.next){case 0:(s=new FileReader).readAsText(r,"UTF-8"),s.onload=function(e){g.parse(e.target.result,{header:!0,complete:function(e){M=e.data,console.log(JSON.stringify(M,null,2))}})};case 3:case"end":return e.stop()}}),e)})))).apply(this,arguments)}function U(e){var r=[];return o.forEach((function(s){s.Answer.indexOf(e)>-1&&r.push(s)})),r}function D(e,r){var s=[];return r.forEach((function(r){if(s.length!=e)s.push(r);else for(var t=0;t<s.length;t++)s[t].Answer.length>r.Answer.length&&(s[t]=r)})),s}function p(e){Q();var r=parseInt(Math.random()*o.length),s=o[r].Answer,t=function(e){var r=arguments.length>1&&void 0!==arguments[1]&&arguments[1],s=[];return Object(S.a)(e).forEach((function(e){var t=U(e),i=(t[t.length-1],D(3,t)),n=parseInt(100*Math.random()%i.length),a={};a=r?{Letter:e,Index:t[n].Answer.indexOf(e),Question:t[n].Question,Answer:t[n].Answer,"Answer Letters":t[n]["Answer Letters"],"Question Letters":t[n]["Question Letters"],Category:t[n].Category,Publisher:t[n].Publisher,Series:t[n].Series,Universe:t[n].Universe,Difficulty:t[n].Difficulty}:{Letter:e,Index:t[n].Answer.indexOf(e),Question:t[n].Question,Answer:t[n].Answer},s.push(a)})),s}(s);return Object(l.jsx)(f,{word:s,data:t})}var b=function(e){e&&e instanceof Function&&s.e(3).then(s.bind(null,22)).then((function(r){var s=r.getCLS,t=r.getFID,i=r.getFCP,n=r.getLCP,a=r.getTTFB;s(e),t(e),i(e),n(e),a(e)}))};a.a.render(Object(l.jsx)(i.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(l.jsx)(p,{})}),document.getElementById("root")),b()}},[[21,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.cb1862a8.chunk.js.map